Your IP: 159.223.154.84 - Unknown · ISP: Unknown · Your Status: Unknown

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Updated: 23 November 2023_

Welcome to FreeVPN.us ("we," "us," or "our"). This Privacy Policy outlines our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information when you use our website [https://www.freevpn.us](https://www.freevpn.us/) (the "Service"). By accessing or using the Service, you agree to the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy

##### 1\. Information We Collect

1. **Usage Data:** We may collect information about how you access and use the Service, including your IP address, browser type, and other usage details.
2. **AdSense:** We use Google AdSense to serve advertisements. AdSense may collect certain information for ad personalization. Please refer to Google's Privacy & Terms for more information: [Google Privacy & Terms](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US).
3. **Cloudflare:** We use Cloudflare to optimize website performance and provide security features. Cloudflare may collect certain data, and their practices are governed by their privacy policy. Please refer to Cloudflare's Privacy Policy for more information: [Cloudflare Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

##### 2\. Use of Information

We use the collected information for various purposes, including:

1. To provide, maintain, and improve the Service.
2. To respond to your inquiries, comments, or questions.
3. To serve personalized advertisements through AdSense.
4. To optimize website performance and security through Cloudflare.

##### 3\. Data Security

We implement reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction.

##### 4\. Cookies

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to enhance your experience on the Service. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

##### 5\. Third-Party Links

The Service may contain links to third-party websites or services that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those third parties.

##### 6\. Disclosure of Information

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities.

##### 7\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting on this page.

##### 8\. Your Choices

You may opt-out of personalized advertising through AdSense by adjusting your ad settings. You can also opt-out of Cloudflare data collection by adjusting your browser settings or visiting Cloudflare's [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/).

##### 9\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://freevpn.us/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Cookie Notice

This website use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.

I understand [Privacy Policy](https://www.freevpn.us/pages/privacy-policy.html)

Welcome to FreeVPN Ask us anything

Hi, can i help you?

##### Help Keep Us Free

FreeVPN.us is dedicated to providing free and fast VPN services to users worldwide. Your generous contribution helps us maintain and expand our servers and services. With your support, we can keep FreeVPN.us free for everyone. Thank you! 🙏❤️

##### Bitcoin

##### Ethereum (ERC20)

##### USDT (BEP20)

##### Solana (BEP20)

##### Litecoin

##### Dogecoin

### Thank you for your loyalty over the past 8 years.

The following is our total achievement so far.

61.234 224 today

User registered

16

Premium User

10.219

Active account

1.933.915 1.034 today

Account created

[

FreeVPN
-------](https://freevpn.us/)

Since 2016, FreeVPN.us has been dedicated to offering a free VPN service with the mission of promoting "Freedom of the Internet." Our goal is to give users unrestricted access to all online content through a reliable and secure connection.

Service

Help

Tools

* * *

All Transactions are 100% Safe and Secure!

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

2016 - 2024 © [Roosterkid](https://roosterkid.com/) x FreeVPN.us made with in

page loaded in 0.010 seconds
